<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>11ty-hax</title>
  <link href="https://abbeylyle4.github.io/11ty-hax/atom.xml" rel="self" />
  <subtitle>project documentation</subtitle>
  <updated>2022-02-27T21:08:42.447-00:00</updated>
  <author>
      <name>abbeylyle4</name>
  </author>
  <id>https://abbeylyle4.github.io/11ty-hax/atom.xml</id>
  <entry>
    <title>About</title>
    <id>https://abbeylyle4.github.io/11ty-hax/content/about/</id>
    <updated>2022-02-27T21:08:42.447-00:00</updated>
    <published>2022-02-27T21:08:42.447-00:00</published>
    <summary></summary>
    <link href="https://abbeylyle4.github.io/11ty-hax/content/about/"/>
    <content type="html">
      &lt;p&gt;My name is Abbey Lyle and I am a senior at Penn State.
&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Getting Started with JavaScript</title>
    <id>https://abbeylyle4.github.io/11ty-hax/content/blogpost1/</id>
    <updated>2022-02-27T21:08:42.447-00:00</updated>
    <published>2022-02-27T21:08:42.447-00:00</published>
    <summary></summary>
    <link href="https://abbeylyle4.github.io/11ty-hax/content/blogpost1/"/>
    <content type="html">
      &lt;h3&gt;VS Code&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VS code is a code editing software that comes in handy when learning JavaScript. It provides support for debugging and version control. It is a great option for beginners who are getting into web dev. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Node JS&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NodeJS is an open source platform and allows you to run server-side applications on your personal machine.
&lt;p&gt;When downloading, make sure that you download the LTS/&amp;quot;recommended for most users&amp;quot; option for a more reliable platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tip&lt;/strong&gt;: to double check that NodeJS has installed successfully, you can simply type &lt;code&gt;node&lt;/code&gt; in your terminal window (for macOS users, you can navigate to it by searching &#39;terminal&#39; in your launchpad)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NPM&lt;/h3&gt;  
&lt;p&gt;
Luckily for you, npm (node package manager) is installed as a _package deal_ with NodeJS. Npm is the default package manager for NodeJS and allows you to use third party code in your own. It is one of the largest software registries, giving you a plethora of tools for your own code.
&lt;p&gt;Similarly to NodeJS, you can ensure you have npm by typing &lt;code&gt;npm&lt;/code&gt; in your terminal window. You will see a longer message this time showing some of the capabilities you have with npm!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Get involved!</title>
    <id>https://abbeylyle4.github.io/11ty-hax/content/contact/</id>
    <updated>2022-02-27T21:08:42.447-00:00</updated>
    <published>2022-02-27T21:08:42.447-00:00</published>
    <summary></summary>
    <link href="https://abbeylyle4.github.io/11ty-hax/content/contact/"/>
    <content type="html">
      &lt;p&gt;The HAXTheWeb team hangs out on slack and would love to chat about all things 11ty, HAX11ty, HAX, and beyond. HAX11ty is one of many creations in the HAX universe and we&#39;d love to hear from those using it. &lt;a href=&quot;https://bit.ly/haxslack&quot;&gt;Join us on slack today!&lt;/a&gt; or follow us on twitter &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/haxtheweb&quot;&gt;@HAXTheWeb&lt;/a&gt;

    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>